Hello friends welcome to all of you again in a new video
request for friends who are new to the channel
please subscribe the channel and press the notification icon then
you will get mutual fund and sumix related all information at the same place in my channel friends
today I will talk about insurance
I have presented to you what is searched on esper youtube then listen to the insurance don't skip the video
if with everything if everything
is needed If there is, insurance is also needed. Insurance
is also important. It can be your term plan, which
can be your savings plan, it can be your unit link plan or investment plan or any
return plan. It varies according to your choice. So
friends, I request you to watch the video with full attention. You will watch the
video
half-heartedly. You will not invest while watching half-heartedly
. Offcourse you will request the whole video and you
can share this information to others if you like
it friends there are many types of plans in insurance
take your term plan if I go to the book in your language take the term plan or
take any traditional plan that you have savings plan fixed endowment plan
take such a plan fixed gives money back return
or you have an investment plan so today I am mainly talking to you about investment
plan Let's talk, friends, today I will talk
about ICIC Prudential Mutual Fund,
there are very few people who don't know
about ICIC Prudential Mutual Fund ,
they sell insurance along with banking services as well as mutual funds. Friends,
there are some reasons to tell you about this plan. Say all
or banking services, all but provide expensive services, this is
the overall plan that I will talk about today.
About ICCI unit link plan,
there are some reasons
why you should invest
in this unit link plan.
The return will be your tax fee return and the second
that here but any of you that maturity after so many years
can not be withdrawn before the
maturity after so many years
in other insurance plans
but it will work like a transparent savings account
. Savings which you
can withdraw after your five years and whenever you withdraw from your fund value,
you will get the money by deducting it from the fund value you have and the whole amount but
paying
tax
and getting second .
According to you can choose the term and premium payment term, it
means how many years you will deposit and after how many years you will withdraw the money, you
can choose it, you can
choose another important thing, friends
, many of us know that friends once
you give money
, it means whether it is your agent or
employee or from the bank.
I will discuss
in details, if you deposit money once in this place, but your
money does not go to the discounted
fund, after five years,
the money automatically
comes to you . And there you
get a three to four percent return on a discount fund. Friends unit link plan
has various charges like fund management charges, fund allocation charges, mortality charges,
administration charges, all these charges, even after all these charges,
it provides you with a good return, but it varies
from plan to plan. I will show you that it
gives percentage return
and if there is anything uncovered in this plan you
will definitely tell me but if there is a query you will definitely tell me where to buy it
from the bank or online if you have an agent you
can buy it from the agent yes friends here with the mutual fund agent or there when
there is a difference in the return here but there is no difference in insurance
but if you purchase online from the website then
you can go there in some plans of ICC Protential. If there is a discount then friends let's go then
friends let me tell you once what is your eligibility criteria
watch the whole video then you
will understand the details of the whole policy There are many types of this insurance plan this insurance plan has many types
of funds I will discuss the percentage of returns of the funds
so please watch the whole video carefully then
you will know the answer to all the questions Presenting you the Isis Prudential Smart Life
Plan Friends so far Don't skip watching the whole video
then you will understand the details of the entire policy.
There are many types of insurance plans.
There are many types of funds.
I will discuss the percentage
returns of the funds. So please watch
the entire video
carefully. Then you will know the answers to all the questions.
If you are 20 to 49 years old then you have to pay
45000 per annum premium here if you are 50 to 52
years old you have to pay about 1 lakh 20 thousand annual premium
and if you are 53 to 54 years old then you have to pay 5 lakh taka annual premium
here and maximum you have to pay here You can pay unlimited and
you can pay this premium half yearly monthly quarterly yearly you
can pay premium in any mode and minimum policy term you
can take 10 years and maximum policy term you can take up to 25 years
your minimum age is 20 years your maximum age is 54 years you are minimum age for maturity it
comes automatically same and friends is another important So your
minimum premium is a matter of summation because it is a depth coverage
that if your premium is from 20 to 44 years then
you are roughly seven times
your annualized
premium means if your premium is Rs
. You will see the premium then you will see your summation
then it will come to you when you do the benefit restatement
it is definitely important to you but here at the moment it is
not that important another thing if you once one may if you
deposit one time premium one lakh 25 thousand you can deposit one time premium
and minimum premium one pay and in other case you 48000 you can pay one pay
policy term you can take 10 years you can take minimum entry age maximum entry
age I am 20 years 54 years your 30 years 64 years
you can take age maturity and tax benefit friends I have told you
I have tax benefit friends tax benefit I have told you this policy
has tax benefit if you can pay premium of Rs
. The main important thing about the policy is the funds,
what funds are there in the policy and how much return those funds have given. Before going,
I will discuss some charges and charges with you guys, this is Uniton.
Some of the plans have boosters so every policy year
you will get 025% booster and edition when you reach maturity when
you pay your full payment premium you will see your 025% from full
if you pay full payment premium or up to six years you
will see premium for five years or after five years you will see a booster of 025% and
if wealth booster every five years you will see premium If you do one pay then
you will get 15% booster and if limited regular pay you
will get 35% booster so roughly here one is giving you booster which is very
important friends it becomes important for another policy here when you
go to buy policy you will see here you have a calculation of 4% and
you have a calculation of 8% 15 years coverage and your premium is ৳50000
so by default your
that If you have Samseor it will be five lakh taka means ten times it automatically
you will see like this so here is a benefit illustration given to you
here if you pay attention here is 50000 taka premium you
are paying premium early and samanseor is your 10 times means five lakh taka it is your
automatically you will get to know increase means your age is 35 years and 15
years policy here is a non guaranteed One is if something happens to you then
you have 4% rate of return means if something happens to you company or if any
problem happens then you will get 8 lakh 53629 rupees from IRD or
as a security and
if at 8% rate if company gives return then it will get 11 lakh 93 thousand rupees it
declines from IIDA that this return you
can show no more return then what are unitly pans Either you will get much more return from this,
much more return, now friends, I have told you one more thing that
there is nothing to fear about the charges, if there are any charges, here
are the
premium
allocation charges.
If you deposit half yearly total premium then you will get 4% charge in one year
4% in two years and 35% in three years and after four years 3% in four to five years and
after six years you will get 2% charge and if you topup then you will get 2% charge and
if you purchase this plan online then your 1% you
will get less than allocation charges here friends if you see in this plan
in a fund here if you have If you pay in half yearly mode but
you will be more benefited because here in year yearly mode sorry here if
you pay in yearly mode but you have to pay 6% charge
more than that but you don't have to pay after one year go to two years your 5% and from then on
but it will decrease so I hope you can buy this plan annually only you can buy this plan
in your annual mode or by default you can buy it in monthly mode
friends after that The return that will be shown after all these charges is your return
here is the fund management charges which all the funds have approximately 13 35% and
the market money market this fund has at least 75% now the policy administration
charges here is point zero 21% per month you will see the charges here
above the annual premium it is the administration charges and if one pay is 60
rupees you will see the charges and the mortality charges Friends, it depends a lot
on the age. Any fixed calculation is given here.
If you are male, then if you are 30 years old, then 18% is deducted. If you are 40, then 32%
is given and if male is female, then 17%
is charged
.
Another thing becomes important friends that's why I suggest friends
here there are many funds you will see there are many types of funds according to your choice according to your
risk you can take different funds so friends if you look here
here is bluechip fund which is basically one kind of index fund NAB is running
4710 rupees NAB is running from 2009
it has given 11% return all your charges which are all deduct
But Focused 50 Fund gave you 11% return here is your top 50 if
company index 50 top 50 company started in 2019 provided 14% return
India Growth Fund gave 18% return here started in 2019
Maximize India Fund provided 12 return if your
started in 2015 and if your best fund Here I want to say that it has launched in 2024
friends so far 12 nab has provided 21% return that is
your best fund so you can buy this insurance plan whenever you
want Midcap 150 Momentum 50 index fund you can go here
Top 50 midcap companies will mainly invest in those companies now
if midcap companies invest here 40% you can see your return
here in midcap index fund your 42% so you can take any fund within these funds and
you can see how much return those funds have given since when they started
friends and
as an investor if you compare with other instruments
apart from mutual fund apart from stock market you
can be mutual fund if you compare any instrument but This mutual
fund this insurance plan will fulfill all your problems
now if I see 12% return provided Multicap growth fund
was started in 2009 and then the company has brought many different funds here for you you
can go to any fund within all the funds and friends if you think
this fund is not performing you can switch the funds which are by default
and mutual fund Return total return if you want to see
that is the best option here you have only one downside that is
the locking period of five years also personally I
have investment in ULI plan I will say this is my personal opinion friends if you
have to get insurance then you can get insurance in unit link plan
where you will also save tax and the previous ULI plans which
do not provide you good returns now is the time. No, the present yuli
plans are bringing you returns even by competing with the market which
often beats the mutual fund and provides better returns than its benchmark market,
so I say you can invest in any fund of your choice,
but of course you can invest on your own responsibility
, you can go for midcap index funds, your 14 rupees is right where you have
midcap. There are 150 Momentum Firms which fund is Midcap 150 Momentum Firms
12 rupees provide 21% return here you can go to any fund and off course
when you do it you can do it by yourself or you can talk to
your insurance consultant and if there is any problem you
can feel free to comment me I will help you as much as possible I
will help you those who didn't like it I will definitely subscribe
to you I hope Jai Hind will be fine and healthy